const quizDB = [
    {
        question: "Q1: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: `Q2: `,
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q3: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q4: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q5: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q6: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: "Q7: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q8: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q9: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: "Q10: ",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        ans: "ans1"
    }
];